LAZARO GABRIEL ONOFRE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

email: lazarogabriel2000@gmail.com phone number: +54 9 11 2389-2175

website: lazarogabriel.github.io/personalsite

linkedIn: lazaro-onofre

SUMMARY

Lover of software development good practices. **Dev Ops** enthusiast. Autodidact and resolutive character. Good communication and team working oriented.

I have experience working with technologies like: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, C#, SQL, ReactJS, .NET Core, .NET Framework, WPF, Docker and Linux.

EDUCATION

<u>Certifications and diplomas</u> - 2018 to forever In course.

<u>Digital House</u> - 2019 to 2019 Desarrollo Web Full Stack.

Universidad Nacional de Lanús - 2019 to 2020

Licenciatura en Sistemas.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GOIAR - January 2020 Full Stack Developer.

ARQCO Constructora S.A.S - Dec. 2018 to Feb. 2019

Freelance website.

D & S Frio y Calor - Aug. 2018 to Nov. 2018

Freelance website.

LANGUAGES

English (intermediate), Spanish (native)

HOBBIES

- Movies and series.
- Software and hardware technology in general.
- Gaming (Chess, Sudoku, Counter-Strike, Valorant).